=The Truth (Season 4)=
(New bonus scenes)
(Snack time gets lively)
He's tall. Give him two.
(Tall guy special)
Thanks.
He's tall too.
Here, this one's for you.
(Tall guys get double)
No.
Keep it for yourself.
This one's matcha.
Yep.
What's matcha, everyone?
(Knowledge +1)
It's tea that's been ground into powder.
(So that's what it is)
Someone's been into yours.
Really?
Where's your matcha?
Where's his matcha?
This is Tieguanyin.
Not matcha.
(The truth is finally revealed)
So Tieguanyin isn't tea?
It is tea.
Yeah, they're all tea.
It's just tea powder.
There's a piece
of seaweed underneath this.
(What does that mean?)
What's that for?
For extra flavor.
(An experienced foodie)
It brings out the aroma.
What do you guys think?
(One bite and you're speechless)
It's good.
(Added to the must-try list)
Not bad.
This is dried pineapple.
(Save the best for last)
Got it. I'll save it for New Year's.
(This is getting way off track)
Save it for your next life.
(What do you mean?)
Save it for the next life?
(Exactly)
For you.
For me?
They're coming after you.
(Twelve out of ten suspicious)
Do you guys know something?
Let's stop cursing Chancellor Tui
all the time,
okay?
We wish you happiness
and good health in your next life.
(Why does that blessing sound so weird?)
Come on, let's toast
with some dried pineapple.
Cheers.
(Full ceremony mode)
Come on.
Okay.
(Can't tell who's in charge)
What do you mean?
(A friendly reminder)
Chancellor Tui's chopsticks.
(Enjoying the chaos)
Your people don't respect you.
(Top-notch service)
What does that mean?
(Five-star service)
He brushed all the crumbs off for us.
He must've worked in customer service
since he was a kid.
(That's some serious skill)
He's got great service instincts.
Why not change the tablecloth?
Just flip the table over.
And there's a performance too?
What does that mean?
That part can be pulled.
Pull it apart.
Pull it. Yeah.
No.
Just look at him.
(The sheltered noble)
He knows nothing about everyday life.
Yeah, he's never done any real work.
You guys are so clueless.
Go help the man already.
(At least someone noticed)
He's so weird.
Do you want to pull this up?
No, leave it.
Okay, leave it.
Leave it.
No more pulling.
It's Prague now.
Now that we've eaten
our fill,
(Time to get down to business)
let's talk business.
(Tui City young heroes' chit-chat time)
I didn't notice yesterday
that there was something on this knife.
I spent so long messing with it.
Man...
What a shame.
I'm so pissed.
And I just happened
to take the two weapons you use most.
Exactly.
It was in the sword slot.
Oh, in the sword slot.
Yeah.
Look.
So it's like this?
That's clearly from being struck.
Yeah.
It's just
a mark left behind.
But it's pretty silver too.
Once I figured out the murder method,
I started wondering
if we should look for the murder weapon.
If we find the murder weapon,
it could point straight to you.
Not a good day to make a move.
What's with your outfit today?
Doesn't he look like Uncle Wuzhu
from "Joy of Life"?
Right?
Yeah.
How did your outfit give you pecs?
(Helping fix his clothes)
It's too loose.
Why did you pull my pants out?
(Starting to investigate the outfit)
It's probably too loose.
What's going on?
Why doesn't it fit right?
Our belts are the same.
Really?
Is it this one?
Why does it look so bulky?
It's because this part
isn't pulled flat.
It looks like you're hiding
a lot of things here.
A lot of secrets.
(Jin's humor)
(Serious recap)
Don't look, little killer.
Yeah.
She's been studying the script all day.
(He will explain it to you)
The killer's script is complicated.
She has to pick and choose.
(Evil whispering)
Oh, stop talking.
(Just see if I stab you)
Let's go.
I'm your big brother.
I'm on a killing spree.
You've completely lost it.
Let's check out Chivalry Manor now.
Once we're inside,
you go first.
I've got my guards.
(Detective team looking out
for each other while scared)
(Night vision mode)
Come on, guys.
(Eyes tightly shut)
What are we supposed to do?
(Horror elements for fictional use)
The candle's lit.
Wait.
(Jin is scared)
What's going on?
It's okay.
(Ning's guess)
The ghost soldiers should come out.
But we...
We might be the ghost soldiers.
No way.
We must've turned
into ghost soldiers already.
There's only one living person among us.
(What?)
(Successfully made the others laugh)
What are you scared of?
It's lit up inside.
Look inside.
(The atmosphere is intense)
Red light.
The back.
Behind you.
This side.
(Imaginations are running wild)
Are two people supposed to lie in here?
(Ke steps up)
Don't rush. Let me take a look, okay?
Let's go together.
Wait.
Watch out for the steps.
(So scared she's stuttering)
Jin, I really...
(Ning is right beside you)
Come on, go find Ning.
I don't know where he is.
(Ning comes to get you)
Come back.
Where is everyone?
(Something big is coming. Memorial)
(Holding tight)
It's okay.
The ghost soldiers are here.
Stand up.
(Caring)
Don't step on her.
You grab her.
Grab her.
Okay.
I'll give you my arm.
(The best Ning)
Hold on.
He...
He is...
(Closing in step by step)
Okay.
Hold on.
(Ke comes to protect you)
It's okay.
(Really scared)
Jin, I was so scared I almost cried.
(Trying to convince them)
We're all ghost soldiers.
We're on the same side.
Stop.
What?
Careful.
(Safe for now)
It's okay.
(Ding has grown braver)
Where is he driving us?
He's trying to get us inside.
Wait, let me check.
See if it opens.
Let's open the door.
We can go in.
Okay, okay, let's go in.
(Winning over the soldiers with love)
(Ning scares everyone)
The alchemy room has test zombies.
(A little scary)
They're all super soldiers.
Don't you have a way to deal
with super soldiers?
(Generating power with love)
Give them a deep kiss.
(A little too much like a romance)
Exactly. We cure them with love.
Just kiss them and they'll be cured.
(Does it work)
(like this?)
(Kiss to clear the way)
When the time comes, just kiss them.
(Kissing the situation under control)
So that's what you meant.
Kiss to clear the way.
What was the Crown Prince writing?
(Focused)
I was writing this character.
Go out this way.
Go out.
This way, right?
I can't see anything.
Go out and cross the bridge.
Go out and turn right.
Then go up and turn left.
Right.
Turn left, go up, then turn left again.
Let's go.
Go.
(Detective team makes good use
of Massage Card)
You have so many cards.
(Ding's: Item, Hint, Dancing, Massage+2)
Dancing, Massage Card.
They're all useless.
(Ning takes a look)
Take a look yourself.
What cards are those?
Two Massage Cards.
(Thinking outside the box)
We can use these on the ghost soldiers.
Right.
Have the Princess and Crown Prince
(Unique service)
take turns massaging you later.
Have the ghost soldiers massage you.
Yeah, let them massage you.
It's so exhausted.
Why not use a Massage Card?
Do it yourself?
(Not enough)
It only lasts three minutes.
(Ke has an idea)
I think next time you should like...
I mean,
when you meet some really powerful NPC,
like someone who's truly supreme,
some kind of revered master,
just tell them to give you a massage.
Then they actually do it.
But what if
they lose control and get angry
afterward?
(Pleasure first)
That's okay. Let's enjoy it first.
Say you run into a deadly challenge.
(Just enjoy it)
Enjoy it first before dealing with it.
You should've had
the ghost soldiers massage you.
(Hardcore massage booked)
Three minutes of that is like thirty.
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(SVIP updates Wed & Thu at 12PM.)
(VIP updates next day at 12PM,
one week early.)